people like him are are attractive to
the CIA because the CIA does need a
pathy when they do these operations.
They do need that element of denial
where where they can just say, "No, it
wasn't us. It was this nut from North
Carolina. Look, he's got a long history
of mental illness. We didn't know what
he was doing. He came to us and we said,
"No, you're nuts. We don't want to work
with you." Well, in fact, they probably
had been working with him for for years.
So Ryan Ralph, ladies and gentlemen, um
the guy uh who tr was trying to shoot
Trump at his golf uh golf course in
Florida.
>> Oh, how he how's he doing?
>> He found guilty of trying to assassinate
Trump in Florida. No kidding.
>> No kidding. A federal jury convicted
Ryan Ralph an inate Is that how you
pronounce that? An inate itinerate.
Itinerate building contractor.
>> Really? It says he's an itinerate
builder. I I guess that's his part-time
job. His main job was a CIA hypno idiot.
Um
59year-old itinerate building
contractor. He couldn't be more of a psy
if he started climbing up the country
charts singing crazy. Are you kidding
me?
How do we know that he's a py? Because
we're hearing about him. You never hear
about the real guy. You should know that
by now, right? So here's what the New
York Times says about this. A man who
plotted to kill President Trump last
year and staked him out in one of his
Florida golf courses with a
semi-automatic rifle was found guilty on
Tuesday of attempting to assassinate a
major presidential candidate. A charge
that carries a maximum penalty life in
prison. His name is Ryan W. Roth, 59, an
itinerate building contractor from North
Carolina, was also found guilty of
assaulting a federal officer and several
firearms violations. Really? Okay. Well,
uh, the 12 member jury deliberated for
about two and a half hours following a
fast-moving trial in which Mr. Ralph
chose to defend himself without a
lawyer. So,
if this guy's on MK Ultra or whatever
they're calling it tonight, after the
verdict was read in court, Mr. Ralph
appeared to try to stab himself in the
neck several times with a pen. Several
United States marshals restrained him
and removed him from the courtroom. He
returned a few minutes later, shackled
and escorted by marshals. His neck tie
and jacket had been removed, but he did
not appear to be injured. Oh, that's
nice. Isn't that nice to know? Uh,
interesting defense strategy. Uh,
prosecutors said that on September 15th,
2024, Mr. Ralph pointed his rifle with
its serial number scratched off at a
Secret Service agent who spotted him in
the shrubbery at the Trump International
Golf Cold West Palm Beach. Mr. Deni, he
denied that he ever took aim at anyone.
The agent fired at him and Mr. Ralph
fled without firing any shots of his
own. The police stopped him about 45
minutes later driving north on
Interstate 95. I'm pretty sure he he
didn't have license plates. I I it's
foggy, but I'm pretty sure makes no make
no mistake. The defendant was going to
kill Donald Trump. Christopher B. Brown,
one of the federal prosecutors, said
during the closing argument, the
defendant was just one bullet away.
Attorney General Pam Bondi said in a
statement after the verdict that Mr.
Rout's conviction illustrated the
Justice Department's commitment to
punishing those who engage in political
violence. This attempted assassination
was not only an attack on our president,
but an affront to our very nation
itself, she said, "Oh, she's very good."
The rare trial of wouldbe presidential
assassin was made more unusual because
Mr. Ralph chose to represent himself
without a lawyer. His decision made the
trial a lopsided one from the start when
judge Ailen M. Canon cut off Mr. Ralph's
opening statement for lack of relevance.
Mr. Ralph's brief brief cross uh
cross-examinate cross-examination of
prosecution witnesses and the small
number of defense witnesses he called
made the trial much shorter than
expected lasting just 12 days. Well, I
just want to let you know there's some
weird stuff about this guy. So, this is
one of the weird things about him. He's
been arrested like a hundred times and
he's never spent any time in jail. And
this is
>> gunfights with cops in North Carolina.
That's a normal thing, right?
>> This is originally from 2002. was
updated in 2015. An armed man was
arrested Monday morning after
barricading himself in a business during
a three-hour standoff. Ryan Ralph,
third, he was 36 then, was arrested
without incident at 1:00 a.m. Monday at
United Roofing. Greensboro police said
Ralph was pulled over about 10 p.m.
Sunday during a traffic stop, but he put
his hand on a firearm and drove to
United Roofing where he remained
barricaded inside. He was charged with
carrying a concealed weapon and
possession of a weapon of mass
destruction. A weapon of mass
destruction. So what what does that
mean? Did he have a bazooka? Referring
Oh, no. Is a fully automatic machine
gun. He was also charged.
>> He was also charged with resisting,
delaying, and obstructing a law
enforcement officer and driving while
license was revoked. Well, that's the
that's really unforgivable. Driving
while his license is is revoked. Come
on. Um, so here's what uh Mike Benz has
to say about this.
>> So Ryan Ralph was basically, you know,
the the 37th leg of a of a CIA rec
paramilitary recruiting operation to top
up human meat fodder in Ukraine. And he
was working with the State Department to
try to convert these passports into no
visas for these fighters. And he was
flagged by Customs and Border Patrol in
June 2023 for this operation. It was
referred to by to DHS HSI, the same
group that that
basically is is implicated uh at least
in in in an indirect fashion, but
potentially even in a direct fashion in
both assassination attempts. HSI refused
to interrogate uh Ryan Ralph when he
returned to the country despite being
flagged to do so by Customs and Border
Patrol. The guy has been arrested almost
a hundred times in his life, but never
spent a day in jail. And most
importantly, 2 and 1/2 weeks ago, this
justice department uh made a public
statement saying it is seeking an
indefinite delay of the trial of Ryan
Ralph because of complex evidence. And
you know why that is? It's because the
complex evidence will reveal that Ryan
Ralph was working his way through a CIA,
DoD, State Department operation to
militarily recruit terrorist fighters
into Ukraine, which is a major
international incident. If revealed, the
Justice Department is protecting the CIA
and the DoD because actually
interrogating the sources of funding
behind Ralph, actually interrogating his
human network is going to implicate the
intelligence community and the defense
department. And that is the second job
of the DOJ. The first job is putting
away the bad guys who but this but the
but the second job is to protect is to
CYA cover the ars of the intelligence
community and the DoD so that the blob's
interests are constantly protected and
concealed from the American people who
could oversee them.
So, I'm interested, John, to get your
take on all of that. And, uh,
um, it certainly seems everything about
this thing seems suspicious. Uh, he's
definitely Do you Do you think he uh,
what do you think about it? And do you
think he was um, somehow
a a victim of mind control?
>> I've read what you've read and what Mike
Benz has read. Um, it was it's my
understanding that what we just heard
from Mike Benz is true.
>> Okay.
>> Mind control. I don't know. It's
possible. I've also read that he had
long-standing mental illness, something
he struggled with for years. But, you
know, even if he was mentally ill, the
issue is people like him are are
attractive to the CIA because the CIA
does need a psych.
They do need that element of denial
where where they can just say, "No, it
wasn't us. It was this nut from North
Carolina. Look, he's got a long history
of mental illness. We didn't know what
he was doing. He came to us and we said,
"No, you're nuts. We don't want to work
with you." Well, in fact, they probably
had been working with him for for years.
So yeah, I I think what Mike Benz is is
telling us in this clip is true, that
this is exactly the kind of person that
the CIA wants to deal with because it
allows them plausible deniability and
every once in a while they really are
nuts and they get themselves into
trouble.
>> And so you think that's what happened?
He he really was nuts and he got himself
into trouble.
>> I do. The the darker one though is what
happened in Butler, Pennsylvania.
>> Yeah. So what what
>> his parents are behavioral therapists.
So that means guilty to me of 100% MK,
you know, Butler, Pennsylvania is is the
first town immediately adjacent to my
hometown.
>> Oh, no kidding.
>> So I went to the Butler Fair and Farm
Show every single year when I was
growing up. We all knew the Butler
Fairgrounds. We all knew about the
flatness of the roofs. For example, that
building that the kid, I forget his
name, was on, uh, that's where they show
the the cows and the hogs and the goats
and the sheep, and you walk through and
they have a blue ribbon and a yellow
ribbon and whatever.
Anybody anybody who knows anything
about a fairgrounds knows that you need
to check the roofs. The roofs are
slightly slanted, so it's easy to get up
there. It's easy to stay up there and
not risk falling off. And they're low,
which makes the shot easier. At the very
least, why not have why not send up a
$25 drone that you can buy at Best Buy
or Target
>> that my kid has with a little camera on
it? Just send up a drone and see if
there's anybody on the roof. And they
didn't bother to do that. You know, I
said earlier that, you know, one of the
unfortunate truths is that so many
government workers in positions of of
import have their heads up their asses,
but that can't be the excuse every
single time, right?
>> Right.
>> It can't.
>> Are you aware, John, that a lot of them
were HHS on loan and not actual Secret
Service and that's why you had fat lunch
ladies?
>> You're exactly right. You're exactly
right. That's what happened. And then
they say, well, you know, the Secret
Service has been in this period of
turmoil and there's been turnover in
leadership and no, come on. The Secret
Service has been around since what?
1878,
right? 1878. You think they'd have their
their act together by now?
Come on. Well, Kimberly Cheeles, the COG
chick that took Cheney down into the
underground bunker the day he shot that
plane out of the sky. That's right.
That's how uh this guy, another thing
about him, his son, as you know, went
down for running a child pornography
network. He's got the trademark
two-color hair of the monarch slave. Why
would he be in charge of running
anything in other countries for the CIA
when he comes off like he's Forest Gump,
frankly, like a slowpoke? He looks like
a hypnotic uh idiot is what he looks
like. But they put him in charge all
this stuff of recruiting. Who would he
recruit? You know, I I got to I got to
take the opportunity to to take a slap
at Malcolm Nance, too.
>> Okay.
>> Malcolm Nance is this guy. He's the
MSNBC counterterrorism uh uh consultant.
>> He he went Didn't he even go to fight
and
>> he he went to fight and when he when he
got there and released the picture of
himself with his M4? It had no magazine
in it.
>> It was just a prop. And he was on the
Polish border. He was nowhere near the
fighting. But um but that's who the
agency attracts. They want they want
Americans
they they want to attract Americans who
are willing to be played and who are
willing to be used. And sometimes
they're smart enough to monetize it like
Malcolm Nance. And sometimes they're
morons like this guy and they just lose
everything and have to stab themselves
in the neck with a pen when they're
found guilty of trying to kill the
president.
Well, sometimes they're a kid whose
family got caught doing something like
Kathy O'Brien said when she came on.
>> That's right.
>> And they get put in the pro. They're a
CIA kid and a bunch of them, he's about
the right age, are still rattling
around.
>> I bet you that Slovakian pre I never
forget that when the Slovakian
president, we did that story. Yes. And
he he wanted to look into Fizer and all
and Ukraine. Next thing you know, I go
stomach.
>> I thought he got shot. I go get shot.
>> Was he shot? Yeah, he got shot. 72y old
man with no history of violence for no
just shoots him and it was this before I
knew the amount of stuff I know about it
now that Smith Montac thing you told us
about which ruin my I mean life by the
way hearing about uh it turns out they
they're balls deep in a lot of stuff and
these kind of idiots remind me the kind
of idiot that would be dating a furry
that you could program over Discord to
go take a shot at Charlie Kirk to make
him a a useful martyr for a larger
entity that was paying for him thinking
this is proprietary technology, I was
told by a ex victim of it. That means
corporate people got it. That means
state actors got it.
>> Uh, and you and I bet you there's like
old models just rattling around like
this.
>> I I bet that's the case. Look at look at
MK Ultra, MK Monarch, MK Chickwit, MK
Worththington, all these all these
operations that were suboperations of MK
Ultra when the CIA and I'll tell you how
it started. It started because of a
disinformation campaign run by the
Russians. So the Russians
the Russians had a had a mole, right?
And they knew there was a CIA mole
amongst them. So they spread this rumor
that the Russians had made incredible
progress in the area of mind control and
that
>> was North Korea. It wasn't a Korea
thing. It was they they they said that
the Koreans were involved, the Chinese
were involved, that there were these
different programs going on at the time
that that allowed them to sort of
approach the threshold where they were
going to be able to create a manurion
candidate. Word got back to the CIA, oh
my god, they said, we're behind. And
they panicked. And that's what led to
the creation of MK Ultra. So they
started with this new invention from
Switzerland called LSD. Let's try dosing
people with LSD. Well, who should we
dose? Hm. Let's dose our own employees
and see what they do. Well, what they do
is they jump off the roof of the hotel
that they're staying in or off the
balcony and they commit suicide. So,
that was a bad idea. Okay, let's cut the
dose. Well, who should we experiment on
next? Well, why don't we recruit a bunch
of prostitutes in San Francisco? We'll
have them pick up John's. will dose the
John's, bring them back to a CIA safe
house in San Francisco and see if they
tell us their innermost secrets. No,
they just went nuts and then they had to
release them back onto the streets of
San Francisco until they're sane again.
And then they said, "Well, what if we
come up with a germ? We'll engineer a
germ and we'll just push it into the air
and see if everybody or anybody gets
sick from this germ." Well, let's do it
in San Francisco because it's foggy in
San Francisco. We already have this safe
house that we that we run the
prostitutes from.
>> They they put this germ. They waited
until an unusually foggy day. They
pushed this germ out into the fog. And
sure enough, 2 days later, 11 people
have to go to the emergency room of
various hospitals with this rare,
not seen before, upper respiratory
infection.
But it didn't get them any closer to
mind control or ESP or remote viewing,
remote sensing and all this other
because it didn't exist. It was
an operation that the Russians had come
up with and we bought it hook, line, and
sinker because of our obsession
with communism.
>> And so
>> I thought the Nazis brought their
knowhow over when we saved a bunch of
them Nazis after the war. Such as
>> Yeah, we gave them allas. Gave them all
visas.
in Alexandria, Virginia. Now,
>> well, when they learned in this very
real thing, MK Monarch that they say is
real, they learned that generational
monarch butterflies generational trauma.
>> That's right.
>> So, no, my control is real. The part
that they're ahead of us over there is a
lie. Obviously, like much like direct
energy weapons,
>> right?
>> Cuba has a direct energy weapon that we
don't have and they're using it.
>> Other people.
>> Oh my god.
>> So, no, that stuff goes back. Did the
Secret Service originate when Andrew
Jackson had an attempt on his life? Is
that
>> It was after the Lincoln assassination.
The The first I'm I'm writing a book on
I I've written a book. It's coming out
next month on the this the historic
cemeteries of Washington DC and in
Congressional Cemetery um in Southeast
Washington, the uh the very first head
of the Secret Service who had been
Lincoln's uh Pinkerton guard during the
1860 and 1864 elections became the first
head of the Secret Service. Oh, no
kidding.
>> Yeah. Funny, huh?
>> Inkerton guard. That's amazing.
>> Well, the thing about an actor killing
him I always find interesting cuz when I
used to see Sasha go into character,
Sasha is a very, I would say almost like
afraid guy. Like he made an assistant
take driving lessons to drive him around
safer. But in character,
>> uh, he would never break other than the
time, you know, in Israel.
>> He would never break and he was gone.
The dude was gone and it was the most
eerie thing I've ever seen. And the
other writer goes, "Boy, that's creepy
as hell, isn't it when he does that?"
Cuz he's in character.
>> Yeah.
>> So John Wils Booth was an actor. All
these people have this thing about him
where they look like up Disney
kids. So that's where the hypnosis and I
think the mind control works real well.
And my evidence for that is no one can
remember anything from more than a
goddamn month ago that I talked to. And
I don't think that's normal. And now we
know chemtrails are real. They came out
and said that's geoengineering. Now it
turns out the fluoride does your
brain up. The goal of every society,
Gorvidal said, is total control. And
that's what that guy, who's the guy
said, when you believe everything wrong,
we know we did our job.
>> Yeah. William,
>> he get killed, I believe. Bill KBY.
>> Yeah. Bill Ky,
>> the head of the CA.
>> They got windup toy assassins, Sir Hans,
Sirhans all over the place.
>> He's one of the best examples.
>> So, he doesn't even And he doesn't
remember.
>> He doesn't remember.
>> So, we know that the CIA was was
experimenting at one of the community
colleges. I don't remember which one it
is here in in Los Angeles when he was
enrolled at that university.
>> Oh, no kidding.
>> Now, we don't know. And I'll tell you
why we don't know if he was specifically
um MK Ultra. Because after Frank Church
directly told the CIA director, "Do not
destroy the documents." He went straight
back to headquarters and told them,
"Destroy everything." So, we only have
about 20% of the MK uh Ultra Stopped.
Yeah.
>> They stopped doing that and didn't
perfect it.
>> They had to piece it together through
some of the financial records that were
that were left over. Right.
>> That's right.
>> And so so you're not saying that the CIA
and the deep state doesn't have uh a
mind control program. They do, right?
>> You know, I I would have to assume that
they do. I mean otherwise, why have a
directorate of science and technology?
Why why spend millions of dollars to
start up uh Palunteer and and these
other these other super secret high-tech
uh companies?
>> Okay.
>> They got to be working on something.
>> Yeah, I'm with you. So, do you have to
go? It's 5:39.
>> I do. I am. I apologize.
>> No, it's I'm sorry we had that technical
problem. There are so many more things I
wanted to ask you about.
>> So, good to see you, though.
>> Great to see you, too. All right.
>> Very interesting, man.
>> Good to see I appreciate you coming in
and like when your book comes out,
please come on. We'd love to have you.
>> So, Utah and Florida just passed bills
to ban fluoride in the water supply. Why
are all these states suddenly doing a
massive U-turn on fluoride when they've
been adding it to our water for the last
80 years? Well, RFK Junior's been
warning us about fluoride for a while.
And the government now admits to the
fact that fluoride is linked to lower
IQ. In a study done by JAMAMA
pediatrics, one of the top medical
journals, scientists found that fluoride
levels over 2 milligrams per liter of
water cause more than a twopoint drop in
children's IQ scores. That's why we use
Cove Pure to purify our water. Copure is
an awesome water filtration system that
sits on your countertop. You don't have
to drill any holes or call a plumber to
set it up. You just fill it up with tap
water, plug it in, and it gets straight
to work. Their clear wave reverse
osmosis technology is labcertified to
remove up to 99.9%
of impurities in your water. Anything
that isn't water, meaning fluoride,
arsenic, or forever chemicals, all of
that gets filtered out, leaving you with
pure water. And let me tell you, once
you try Cop Pure water, you're never
going back. It's the best tasting water
I've ever had. Plus, what I love about
Cove Pier is it lets you have water
exactly the way you want it. Whatever
temperature you want, just push a
button. Cold, hot, warm, whatever. If
you happen to like fluoride, that's
totally fine. There are tons of ways you
can get that through toothpaste or
mouthwash. But the government should
never force you to ingest it. So, take
back your right to choose. Click the
link in my description box,
covepure.com/jimmy.
And for a limited time only, you'll get
a special discount of $200
off Cove Pure. That's c ov.com/jimm.
Come see me on tour in Hermosa Beach,
Sacramento, San Francisco, Melbourne,
Australia, Sydney, Australia, Brisbane,
Burbank, California the day after
Thanksgiving, and Pottstown,
Pennsylvania. Go to jimmy.com for a link
for tickets.
[Music]